{
    "level5.1":
    [{
        "question":"A group of compromised computers that have software installed by a worm or Trojan is known as which of the following?",
        "answers":["Botnet","Virus","Honeypot","Zombie"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following computer security threats can be updated automatically and remotely? (Select the best answer.)",
        "answers":["Virus","Worm","Zombie","Malware"],
        "correct":2 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is a common symptom of spyware?",
        "answers":["Infected files","Computer shuts down","Applications freeze","Pop-up windows"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is not an example of malicious software?",
        "answers":["Rootkits","Spyware","Viruses","Browser"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following types of malware appears to the user as legitimate but actually enables unauthorized access to the user's computer?",
        "answers":["Worm","Virus","Trojan","Spam"],
        "correct":2 
    }],

    "level5.2":
    [{
        "question":"Which type of attack uses more than one computer?",
        "answers":["Virus","DoS","Worm","DDoS"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"What is a malicious attack that executes at the same time every week?",
        "answers":["Virus","Worm","Ransomware","Logic bomb"],
        "correct":3 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these is true for active interception?",
        "answers":["When a computer is put between a sender and receiver","What a person overhears a conversation","When a person looks through files","When a person hardens an operating system"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"One of your users was not being careful when browsing the Internet. The user was redirected to a warez site where a number of pop-ups appeared. After clicking one pop-up by accident, a drive-by download of unwanted software occurred. What does the download most likely contain?",
        "answers":["Spyware","Smurf","Backdoor","Logic bomb"],
        "correct":0 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following types of malware appears to the user as legitimate but actually enables unauthorized access to the user's computer?",
        "answers":["Worm","Virus","Trojan","Spam"],
        "correct":2 
    }],

    "level5.3":
    [{
        "question":"You are the security administrator for your organization and have just completed a routine server audit. You did not notice any abnormal activity. However, another network security analyst finds connections to unauthorized ports from outside the organization's network. Using security tools, the analyst finds hidden processes that are running on the server. Which of the following has most likely been installed on the server?",
        "answers":["Spam","Rootkit","Backdoor","Ransomware"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"Whitelisting, blacklisting, and closing open relays are all mitigation techniques addressing what kind of threat?",
        "answers":["Spyware","Spam","Viruses","Botnets"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following types of scanners can locate a rootkit on a computer?",
        "answers":["Image scanner","Barcode scanner","Malware scanner","Adware scanner"],
        "correct":2 
    },
    {
        "question":"Dan is a network administrator. One day he notices that his DHCP server is flooded with information. He analyzes it and finds that the information is coming from more than 50 computers on the network. Which of the following is the most likely reason?",
        "answers":["Virus","Worm","Zombie","PHP script"],
        "correct":1 
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following types of malware appears to the user as legitimate but actually enables unauthorized access to the user's computer?",
        "answers":["Worm","Virus","Trojan","Spam"],
        "correct":2 
    }]
}